<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<alumni>
  <profile>
    <name>Justin Koshy</name>
    <slug>justin-koshy</slug>
    <country>India</country>
    <designation>Founder and CEO - Compliance Global Inc</designation>
    <course>MBA - International Business - 2006</course>
    <cdescription>New York based online training organisation</cdescription>
    <quote>My MBA at LSC was a milestone in my personal life and afforded me the confidence to proceed in my professional front. The highlight of LSC is the world-class teaching faculty. These, coupled with extremely talented support staff and campus facilities, made my experiences with LSC possibly the most glorious moments of my life. The vibrant and diverse student community at LSC helped me to connect with students from across the world. I thoroughly enjoyed the LSC experience and will cherish not only the knowledge that I acquired, but also the friendships that I made. I would highly recommend LSC to any student considering an international MBA.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Fabio Monteiro</name>
    <slug>fabio-monteiro</slug>
    <country>Portugal</country>
    <designation>Business Process Outsourcing Leader, Nielsen Media Research - London, UK</designation>
    <course>MBA - Finance – 2008</course>
    <cdescription>Global information and media company</cdescription>
    <quote>In the current global world we live in, there is nothing more important than the ability to understand and successfully navigate throughout multicultural and highly diversified teams. LSC has not only provided an excellent cost/benefit qualification but also the opportunity to work and interact with people all around the word. The MBA title helped me to further develop and consolidate my career in the UK. I now oversee teams in Europe, America and India. Needless to say my MBA was key to all of this.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Oshadee Withanawasam</name>
    <slug>oshadee-withanawasam</slug>
    <country>Sri Lanka</country>
    <designation>Director - Conference Publicity Chair, The International Institute of Knowledge Management (TIIKM) - Sri Lanka</designation>
    <course>MBA – Marketing – 2011</course>
    <cdescription>Knowledge sharing facilitator and conference management organisation</cdescription>
    <quote>LSC life was really enjoyable for me. It gave me a world-reputed experience, good lecturers and friends, knowledge, and international exposure. Moreover, the lessons I learned are important in my life today, and are applicable in my business. My time at LSC was a turning point in my life and added mileage to my career.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Muhammad Bhatti</name>
    <slug>muhammad-bhatti</slug>
    <country>Pakistan</country>
    <designation>Business Review Manager, Ernst and Young - London, UK</designation>
    <course>MBA – International Business – 2010</course>
    <cdescription>Global professional services firm</cdescription>
    <quote>I found LSC as an excellent platform to diversify my business, communication and analytical skills. LSC is an excellent and quality education provider in the town with a very competitive, rather nominal fee structure. LSC is bedecked with an excellent faculty and the courses are taught by learned, highly qualified and experienced professionals. My MBA degree from LSC opened lots of doors for me and helped me to secure one of the top roles in Royal Bank of Scotland.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Lauryn Yuen</name>
    <slug>lauryn-yuen</slug>
    <country>Hong Kong</country>
    <designation>Creative Director, 16print Ltd - London, UK</designation>
    <course>MBA – International Business(SBL) – 2013</course>
    <cdescription>London-based 2D and 3D design company</cdescription>
    <quote>As a recent graduate from LSC, I am proud to say that it offered me a lot of opportunities and support in the development of my study and career. Within the MBA course, Strategic Management and Entrepreneurship (BDP) were my favourite modules which enhanced my knowledge and confidence in the business field. Tutors and professors provided endless assistance, which was one of the most crucial elements for my success.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Anyie Rene Oteh</name>
    <slug>anyie-rene-oteh</slug>
    <country>Tanzania</country>
    <designation>Trade Minerals Manager, SGS Tanzania Superintendence Co Ltd</designation>
    <course>MBA – International Business – 2009</course>
    <cdescription></cdescription>
    <quote>At LSC we were taught to work hard and to be in control of our studies. Our lecturers always made us to believe that we were capable of running Fortune 500 companies. This built my confidence, managerial skills, business mind, and turned me into a strong leader; skills which are helping me today as Trade Minerals Business Manager for SGS Tanzania. I trust LSC's capabilities of creating business leaders so much so that I arranged for my younger sister to study at LSC.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Hasmik Sargsyan</name>
    <slug>hasmik-sargsyan</slug>
    <country>Armenia</country>
    <designation>Chief Marketing Officer, Mini Raxevsky - Armenia</designation>
    <course>MBA – International Business – 2011</course>
    <cdescription>Leading European designer in children's clothing</cdescription>
    <quote>My experience at LSC has played a major role in my life both in terms of the experience in living in London and in making friends of all nationalities, religions and cultures. Due to the skills learned on the course, I managed to climb the career ladder and within just 3 years I am a Senior Marketing Specialist at the leading financial and advisory group in Armenia, Ameria Group. My international experience was a big help in communicating with international partners, coordinating projects across borders and bring my knowledge and skills I gained to my team, supporting them to advance further.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Peter Onokuah</name>
    <slug>peter-onokuah</slug>
    <country>Nigeria</country>
    <designation>Management Trainee, Enterprise - New York, USA</designation>
    <course>BA (Hons) Business Studies – 2013</course>
    <cdescription>Global car and van hire company</cdescription>
    <quote>Studying at LSC was one of the best decisions of my life because the knowledge I gained there has helped build a foundation upon which my present career is built. Every coursework I took prepared me strongly for the corporate world and has set me above my peers. I would never have been as successful without the sound knowledge I learned at LSC.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Sevda Okur</name>
    <slug>sevda-okur</slug>
    <country>Turkey</country>
    <designation>News Producer Presenter, Celebro Media Networks - London, UK</designation>
    <course>MBA – 2012</course>
    <cdescription>International TV production company with offices in London, Paris and Moscow</cdescription>
    <quote>I left a good job in my own country to come to London and make my academic dream come true. Studying a masters degree is challenging, especially in a foreign language. Therefore, the vast improvement in my English was one benefit. Secondly, the help and guidance LSC lecturers aided me on the direction for my career path by advising me to set up my own business, which has become very successful, and use my theoretic knowledge before pursuing my PhD. Thirdly, the knowledge which I gained was invaluable for real life business situations. Lastly, the diversity, not just within the college but in London in general, adds a whole new dimension to your learning due to the friends and contacts you make from around the world. I feel so lucky that I studied at LSC. I enjoyed every single moment.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Timir Jaiswal</name>
    <slug>timir-jaiswal</slug>
    <country>India</country>
    <designation>Vice President - Strategic Marketing, Branding and Sales Management, Global Discovery Academy - India</designation>
    <course>MBA – International Business – 2009</course>
    <cdescription>Group of K-12 schools across India</cdescription>
    <quote>LSC was a great boost in my career and my personality development. The support I received from Dr. Rajendra Kumar and the other academic staff was notable. Upon graduating, I spent five years in the UK in Sales and Education roles. I have since returned to India as Vice President at Global Discovery Academy and recently joined LASSIB Society as Joint Director. Overall my journey at LSC was very exciting and full of learning from the best in the field.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Henry Yamba Kamara</name>
    <slug>henry-yamba-kamara</slug>
    <country>Sierra Leone</country>
    <designation>Managing Director, Sierra Leone Produce Marketing Company (SLPMC) - Sierra Leone</designation>
    <course>PhD, International Trade - Linking Smallholder Farmers to Market – 2014</course>
    <cdescription>Government organisation involved in imports and exports of agricultural produce</cdescription>
    <quote>Completing my studies at LSC provided me the opportunity of meeting highly experienced tutors who inspired and decorated me with the confidence that made me what I am today.  The knowledge and experience gained at the institution helped me secure top jobs with my government. Of utmost importance is the ability of LSC to present itself as a perfect platform for networking; maintaining a multi-cultural global community, with sensitivity and respect for cultural and ethnic diversity.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Muhammad Usman</name>
    <slug>usman</slug>
    <country>Pakistan</country>
    <designation>Managing Director, CHASE Kids University - Pakistan</designation>
    <course>MBA – International Business – 2010</course>
    <cdescription>Children's education institution</cdescription>
    <quote>Studying in LSC was an amazing time for me, a time in which I have learned a lot, which was not possible at any other place. The techniques and methods of the teaching staff at LSC are incredible, and they helped me greatly in every aspect of my life. I am now a Managing Director in a private education centre.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Yathukulan Kanagaratnam</name>
    <slug>yathukulan</slug>
    <country>Sri Lanka</country>
    <designation>Marketing Manager, City Goddess Limited - London, UK</designation>
    <course>BA (Hons) Business Studies – 2011</course>
    <cdescription>London-based wholesale fashion outlet</cdescription>
    <quote>The time I spent at LSC was a truly life-changing experience. I am managing a team of five employees in an online fashion company within two years of graduating. Apart from the strong knowledge and transferable skills that I acquired during education, one of the most important ideas inculcated into my mind by my professors was “dare to dream bold dreams”. I would add “and dare to chase them”. Thank you professors and thank you LSC.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Mega Rohan Madkaikar</name>
    <slug>mega</slug>
    <country>India</country>
    <designation>Assistant Manager, Capri Global Capital Ltd - India</designation>
    <course>MBA - International Business – 2013</course>
    <cdescription>Financial and debt-advisory services organisation</cdescription>
    <quote>I decided to pursue an MBA in International Business because I wanted to take the next step in my career. My experience at LSC has provided the foundation on which to build my career. I have been able to implement what I learned from my MBA, it has helped me to make lots of decisions, and allowed me to make a difference to my organisation. It's about thinking in a leadership way. It's involving people in the decision making process. It's thinking of the bigger picture, and how we can put theory into practice. I credit my success as a Business Development Manager in a leading Chicago based NBFC to my experience at LSC.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Ntongwe Enongene</name>
    <slug>ntongwe</slug>
    <country>Cameroon</country>
    <designation>Associate Regional Director for Africa, IIMP - Ontario, Canada</designation>
    <course>MBA – 2012</course>
    <cdescription>International, professional not-for-profit association dedicated to developing internationally accepted marketing standards</cdescription>
    <quote>I highly recommend LSC to students from Africa and the world at large. The friendly and multicultural environment was a priceless experience and opportunity to study and network with professionals from different countries. Thanks to LSC I was able to earn a UK MBA at an affordable price, thus equipping me with the confidence and skill set to excel in my career.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Mohammed Labeeb Badri</name>
    <slug>labeeb</slug>
    <country>India</country>
    <designation>Operational Analyst, JP Morgan Chase - India</designation>
    <course>MBA – Finance – 2013</course>
    <cdescription>Leading global financial services firm operating in over 60 countries</cdescription>
    <quote>Applying your knowledge and skills is very crucial for survival in today’s rapidly changing environment. At LSC, students not only gain the required knowledge and skills but also learn to apply them effectively when required. On completion of my MBA at LSC, taking on the challenges that a student faces in the corporate space was a smooth ride for me.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Marianna Grigoryan</name>
    <slug>marianna</slug>
    <country>Armenia</country>
    <designation>Finance Supervisor, Marriott International - Edinburgh, UK</designation>
    <course>MBA – Finance – 2011</course>
    <cdescription>Leading lodging and hospitality company that develops, operates and franchises hotels and corporate housing worldwide</cdescription>
    <quote>LSC helped me to make a very well-paid professional step in my life. Since graduating, I have worked in various finance roles in Hilton and Marriott Hotels, and was recently promoted to Finance Supervisor in Marriott Hotels Scotland. It could not be any better.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Sayed Haseeb</name>
    <slug>haseeb</slug>
    <country>Afghanistan</country>
    <designation>Director, Locomotive Logistic and Supply Services - Afghanistan</designation>
    <course>BA (Hons) Business Studies – 2012</course>
    <cdescription>Logistic supply services organisation</cdescription>
    <quote>Whenever I think of my time at London School of Commerce - I remember the beautiful memories attached to that experience; affectionate people with a diverse background, a friendly environment, and the up-to-date and impeccably-taught course (BABS HONS). LSC provides a great and affordable platform for domestic and international students to gain efficient and usable knowledge and experience.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Romena Chowdhury</name>
    <slug>romena</slug>
    <country>Bangladesh</country>
    <designation>Practice Manager, National Health Service (NHS) - London, UK</designation>
    <course>BA (Hons) Business Studies - 2011 and MBA - 2013</course>
    <cdescription>The world's largest public funded health service</cdescription>
    <quote>When I came to LSC, it felt very welcoming. I was certain that it was the college to help me build up my knowledge and career. It was a once in a lifetime experience; the students from all over the world, the vibrant culture, the location at LSC, and the guidance from my teachers.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Anujin Galtbaatar</name>
    <slug>anujin</slug>
    <country>Mongolia</country>
    <designation>Investment Specialist, E.G. River Hydropower Plant Unit - Mongolia</designation>
    <course>BA (Hons) Business Studies - 2011</course>
    <cdescription>Sustainable energy project to build a hydropower station</cdescription>
    <quote>I have been dreaming of working on an environmentally friendly project for my country, Mongolia, ever since the business ethics class and my dissertation for the BABS course at LSC. In late November 2013, the Eg River Hydropower Plant Project got the green light from the government to form a project unit. I had the opportunity to join as the Investment Specialist.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Marino Franinovic</name>
    <slug>marino</slug>
    <country>Croatia</country>
    <designation>CEO, VR Enbekon Ltd. SE Europe - Croatia</designation>
    <course>MBA, International Business - 2011</course>
    <cdescription>Centre of competence for renewable energy projects</cdescription>
    <quote>My MBA at LSC is a very valuable qualification, and gave me the business acumen and forethought to succeed in my role as CEO. I was appointed to this position within a year of graduating from LSC. I made a number of fantastic friends and contacts in the diverse classes within the school, and would certainly recommend studying there.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>David Ebralidze</name>
    <slug>david</slug>
    <country>Georgia</country>
    <designation>Head of Administration, Georgian Co-Investment Fund - Georgia</designation>
    <course>MBA, Marketing - 2009</course>
    <cdescription>USD$6bn private equity investment fund</cdescription>
    <quote>I highly recommend London School of Commerce to all prospective students. LSC provides a unique chance to earn a British MBA with reasonable tuition fees and truly outstanding courses. The culturally diverse community at LSC allowed me to network with students from all over the globe. LSC paved the way to my future professional career.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Tamara Sargsyan</name>
    <slug>tamara</slug>
    <country>Armenia</country>
    <designation>Risk Analyst, ArmSwissbank - Armenia</designation>
    <course>MBA, Finance - 2011</course>
    <cdescription>Leading corporate, investment and private banking institution in Armenia</cdescription>
    <quote>The diversity gave me the opportunity to understand different cultures a fundamental requirement for success in an increasingly global business world. My MBA gave me an opportunity to learn to think in a different way, to develop myself as a leader, and learn how to influence people and get my opinion heard. The experience I gained in the School and in London opened new doors. However, most valuable is the friendship I have built and the network I am now part of.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Syed Hasnain Rizvi</name>
    <slug>hasnain</slug>
    <country>Pakistan</country>
    <designation>Director, Dhaka Group of Educational Institutions (Pvt.) Ltd - Pakistan</designation>
    <course>MBA, Marketing - 2011</course>
    <cdescription>Group of schools in Karachi with 3,000 graduates per year</cdescription>
    <quote>The multi-cultural environment at LSC provided me with the opportunity to meet people from different cultures; a great experience. Moreover, the faculty at LSC comprises of learned, highly qualified and experienced professionals assisted by young and energetic support staff who will put in every effort to train and polish you for the upcoming competitive world.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Reenu Verma</name>
    <slug>reenu</slug>
    <country>Tanzania</country>
    <designation>Business Manager to Chief Marketing Officer, Vodacom Tanzania - Tanzania</designation>
    <course>Business Studies - 2010</course>
    <cdescription>Pan-African mobile telecommunications company with 50 million active customers</cdescription>
    <quote>My experience at LSC was fun, crazy, and educational, mostly because of the professors. I leaned so much about myself during my time there. My advice to students is to make use of all the resources around you at LSC; don't be afraid to ask questions and seek guidance especially from your professors. And don't forget to have fun.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Kamakshi Rathore</name>
    <slug>kamakshi</slug>
    <country>India</country>
    <designation>Senior Analyst, Deutsche Bank - India</designation>
    <course>MBA- Finance- 2012</course>
    <cdescription>German global banking and financial services institution</cdescription>
    <quote>I would highly recommend LSC to any students considering a British MBA. The school is undoubtedly expanding its presence across the globe and has some of the best international faculty. My MBA Degree from LSC helped me to secure a good position with a company as big as Citibank, and that even happened in times of such recent financial uncertainty.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Nainaz Shroff</name>
    <slug>nainaz</slug>
    <country>India</country>
    <designation>Director and Partner, Taylor and Shroff Ltd - UK</designation>
    <course>MBA – International Business – 2007</course>
    <cdescription>Fine wines and spirits brand that exports wine from the UK to India</cdescription>
    <quote>Taylor and Shroff was possible only because my LSC teachers supported and believed in the idea. LSC provides a perfect atmosphere to enhance your management and interpersonal skills.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Thu Trang Nguyen</name>
    <slug>thu</slug>
    <country>Vietnam</country>
    <designation>Sales and Marketing Manager, Vietnam Telecommunication International Company - Vietnam</designation>
    <course>MBA – Marketing – 2010</course>
    <cdescription>Government-owned telecommunication group with over 20,000 employees</cdescription>
    <quote>The Multi-cultural environment at LSC helped me in developing an understanding of behavior traits of people from different countries. This experience has now given me the confidence to work for an international company and tackle clients from different countries.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Frederick V. Massawe</name>
    <slug>frederick</slug>
    <country>Tanzania</country>
    <designation>Export Manager, Tanzania Coffee Board - Tanzania</designation>
    <course>MBA – Marketing – 2006</course>
    <cdescription>Government organisation to regulate and advise the Tanzanian coffee industry</cdescription>
    <quote>The Faculty at LSC was very knowledgeable and helpful on academic as well as administrative matters. I was surprised that our course leader was able to remember the name of each and every student in his batch. This shows how close the faculty are to each student.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Irina Tumanova</name>
    <slug>irina</slug>
    <country>Russia</country>
    <designation>Senior Consultant, Deloitte - Chile</designation>
    <course>MBA – Marketing – 2009</course>
    <cdescription>Largest professional services network in the world by revenue and number of professionals</cdescription>
    <quote>Studying at LSC provided me with the perfect platform to network with students from various countries. Apart from the excellent faculty and facilities at LSC, the cultural diversity helped a great deal in enhancing the learning experience. Varied experiences and knowledge gained during the course were instrumental in shaping my career first with Accenture and then with Deloitte.</quote>
  </profile>
  <profile>
    <name>Himanshu Botadra</name>
    <slug>himanshu</slug>
    <country>India</country>
    <designation>Credit Risk Senior Business Analyst, Citi Group - London, UK</designation>
    <course>MBA – Finance – 2010</course>
    <cdescription>International financial conglomerate with operations in consumer, corporate, investment banking and insurance.</cdescription>
    <quote>Completing an MBA from LSC has given me the confidence to aim higher and the self belief that nothing is impossible. I take this opportunity to thank the staff, counselors and faculty members of LSC for their unconditional support and guiding me to get my Internship with Citi, which has provided me with a perfect launch pad for my career.</quote>
  </profile>
</alumni>
